By adding the meta viewport tag to the head element of
the page we tell the browser that we know what we're doing.
We need to use the meta viewport value with =device-width, which
instructs the page to match the screen's width in device independent pixels.
알려줍니다. 페이지가 매치된다고 화면의 넓이랑 dip로
This allows the page to reflow content to match the screen sizes,
이렇게하면 페이지가 화면 크기와 일치하도록 콘텐츠를 리플로우 할 수 있습니다.
whether rendered on a small mobile device or on the laptop.
작은 기기에서 랜더되거나 랩탑에서 랜더 될 때
Adding the attribute initial-scale=1 instructs the browsers to establish
initial-scale = 1 은 나타냅니다. 브라우저가 확립하는 것을
a one to one relationship between device independent pixels and CSS pixels.
1:1 관계로 dip과 css픽셀을
CSS pixels are what we're used to working with most of the time, and
css pixel은 우리가 사용한 것입니다. item에 적용시기 위해 그리고
really the only one I need to worry about.
정말 오직 하나다 내가 걱정할 필요가 있는
Without initial-scale=1 some browsers will keep the page width
initial-scale=1이 없으면 몇몇 브라우저는 유지할 겁니다. 페이지넓이를
constant when rotating to landscape mode.
일정하게 가로모드로 될 때에도
They also scale the content rather than allowing it to reflow(콘텐츠가 차지하는 공간을 조정).
initial-scale=1이 없는 것을 허용합니다 콘테츠를 크게하는 것 ~보다 그것이 역류하는 것을 허용하는